Welcome, I'm Melissa Dawn Simkins and I am
honored to be your coach through this flagship
experience called the M.V.P. Accelerator Manager Track.
Now you're embarking on a dual journey.
While your direct report is digging deep into their own potential,
you will be right alongside
them, not just as a supervisor, but as a high-performance Player-Coach.
You've officially entered the M.V.P.
Accelerator Manager Track in the Athleadership Arena.
Now, Athleadership is where elite athletic
mindset meets next-level leadership, mastery
to fuel resilience, unlock purpose, and drive lasting performance.
The Athleadership Performance System is our
comprehensive measurement analytics framework
that tracks leadership transformation across the A.R.A.W.
dimensions we call Agility, Resilience,
Alignment, and Wellbeing.
We also call this the Core 4.
Now, it's backed by neuroscience and performance psychology.
It is the science and the soul of our model.
To ensure we're all aligned, let's clarify our key terms.
You'll hear me refer to your direct report as the player or the Athleader.
An Athleader is anyone committed to conditioning
their leadership with the discipline and mindset
of an elite athlete to fuel resilience, unlock purpose, and sustain performance.
And if you've never seen yourself as an athlete,
or if your direct report hasn't either, it's
OK.
This isn't about playing sports or lifting weights.
It's about unlocking the discipline, the mindset,
and the clarity and inner strength already
in you to win from within.
You are the Player-Coach,
participating in your own leadership development while actively
coaching your player.
Our goal is to give you practical frameworks to
make your coaching conversations more impactful,
your team more aligned, and your own leadership more sustainable.
Before we begin, I want to ask you to reflect on
one leadership behavior you want to strengthen
for yourself.
What is one leadership behavior you want to improve
for how you support your team's performance?
Keep this front and center as we go through
this journey and build your own 90-day plan
over the course of this experience.
We'll come back at the end and celebrate your progress.
In our next video,
we'll begin your conditioning by focusing on the most important person you
lead, yourself.